{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "Sample 12",
      "description": "This is Sample 12",
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "name": "Sample 3",
      "description": "Sample 3 Description ",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "Sample Card 6",
      "back": "Back of Sample Card 6",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "This is card 1",
      "back": "Back of card 1",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "eryrey",
      "back": "ryrey",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "front": "Front of Card",
      "back": "Back of Card",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "front": "Front1",
      "back": "Back1",
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "front": "Front 3",
      "back": "Back 3",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "Front 4",
      "back": "Back 4",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 15
    }
  ]
}